hairfinity.com 2015-11-07

# Privacy Policy | Hairfinity US

Brock Beauty, Inc. is totally committed to protecting the privacy of our site visitors and customers. We are customers of other Internet sites and fully appreciate and respect the importance of privacy on the Internet. We will not disclose information about our customers to third parties except where it is part of providing a service to you – e.g. arranging for a product to be sent to you, carrying out credit and other security checks and for the purposes of customer research and profiling or where we have your express permission to do so.

## Collecting Information

## Cookies Policy

Cookies are information files that are sent to your computer or mobile device when you visit a website using that computer or mobile device. It is utilized to recognize your device when you return to the website for future visits. These types of files do a number of different jobs such as remembering your personal preferences and items you may have viewed, assisting us to improve your site experience as well as trying to ensure the advertisements or offers you see online are more relevant to you. Generally, these cookies can be divided into 4 types, each of which is outlined below.

**Strictly Necessary Cookies**

Strictly Necessary Cookies are necessary to enable the website to provide services you have asked for such as remembering your shopping bag items and assisting with checkout.

**Performance Cookies**

Performance Cookies collect anonymous information on how you use the site. The data is then merged with other users’ data to enable Brock Beauty, Inc. to improve how the website operates. We use Google Analytics cookies to help us understand how our customers arrive at our site; browse or use our site; and highlight areas where we can improve such as navigation, shopping experience and marketing campaigns. The data stored by these cookies never reveals personal details from that could establish a user’s personal identity.

**Functionality Cookies**

Functionality Cookies remember choices you make such as language, search parameters such as size or color. These can then be used to provide you with a quicker, more tailored and pleasant experience when returning to our website to order. The information is also merged with other users on an anonymous basis to enable us to improve the functionality of our website.

**Targeting Cookies or Advertising Cookies**

Targeting Cookies or Advertising Cookies collect information about your browsing preferences in order to make our advertising more relevant to you and your interests. They remember the websites you have visited and will share some information with other 3rd parties such as advertisers.

If you are uncomfortable with any of these cookies, you may change the settings on your browser to prevent cookies from being stored on your computer or mobile device without your explicit consent. Please see your browser “help” section for details on how to manage the cookie settings.

By using our websites you accept our use of cookies in accordance with this cookie policy. If you do not accept the use of cookies, please disable them before using our websites.

## Sharing and Use of Information

**Disclosures of your information**

We may disclose your personal information in the event that Brock Beauty, Inc. is acquired by a third party, in which case personal data which we hold about our customers may be one of the transferred assets; or if we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Brock Beauty, Inc., our customers or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

We will not sell your name, address, e-mail address, credit card information or personal information to any third party. It is important to know that we cannot be held responsible or held liable for the actions of third party sites from which you may have been directed to the Brock Beauty, Inc. website or third party websites you may have been directed to by clicking a link found to the Brock Beauty, Inc. website.

**Links to Outside Websites**

Our website may contain links to and from the other affiliate websites, advertisers and other third parties. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that they have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.

## Grow Longer, Stronger Hair

Hairfinity Hair Vitamins are formulated with essential nutrients for healthy hair growth. Our vitamins nourish your hair from the  **inside out**. See results in the first month.

Learn More

## Get a Free Hair Care Regimen

Do you suffer with breakage or shedding? Your hair care regimen may be to blame. Learn which products to use with your Hairfinity Hair Vitamins for the best results.

Get Yours Now

## Place Your Order Online

Ready to get faster growing, longer, stronger hair. Get your Hairfinity Hair Vitamins and the hair products you need to begin your journey to healthier hair.

Order Now
